keo.co.za 2014-06-29

# 

### Privacy Policy

##  SA Rugby Magazine Website Privacy Policy - Summary

_(Version: 1.0)_

**1\. Summary**

We respect your privacy. This is a summary of our privacy policy and contains the most important and relevant points for you. You can read the full privacy policy below.

**2\. Collection**

We collect certain information:

  * on entering competitions,
  * when you make use of our services, necessary to provide the service to you;
  * from your web browser;
  * from cookies we may send to your computer and from web beacons on our website to track how you use our website and to try and give you a personalised experience; and
  * optional information, that you provide when you upload or download content from our website or when you enter competitions, take advantage of promotions, or register and subscribe for certain additional services.

**3\. Use**

We may use your information:

  * to send you administrative messages and email updates to you regarding the website;
  * for marketing purposes.

**4\. Disclosure**

We might disclose your information in the specific circumstances mentioned in this policy.

**5\. Security**

We protect your information in the manner specified in our security policy.

**6\. Your choices**

  * You can turn off cookies in your browser; or
  * You can opt-out of marketing communications with us.

**7\. Contact us**

You can contact us with privacy related questions at [info@hsm.co.za](mailto:info@hsm.co.za) with POPI in the subject line.

##  SA Rugby Magazine Website Privacy Policy

**1\. Audience**

This policy applies to all visitors to our website and customers who have subscribed to the services we offer (“you” and “your”).

**2\. Purpose of this policy**

We respect your privacy and take the protection of personal information very seriously. The purpose of this policy is to describe the way we collect, store, use, and protect information that can be associated with a specific natural or juristic person and can be used to identify that person (“personal information”). Personal information:

2.1 includes

  * certain information collected on entering competitions through Facebook comments (see below); and
  * optional information that you voluntarily provide to us (see below).

2.2 excludes

  * information that has been made anonymous so that it does not identify a specific person;
  * permanently de-identified information that does not relate or cannot be traced back to you specifically; and
  * non-personal statistical information collected and compiled by us and information that you have provided voluntarily in an open, public environment or forum including (without limitation) any blog, chat room, community, classifieds or discussion board. Because the information has been disclosed in a public forum, it is no longer confidential and does not constitute personal information subject to protection under this policy.

**3\. Acceptance of terms**

You must accept all the terms of this policy when you register for any of our services. If you do not agree with anything in this policy, then you may not register for and use any of the services. By accepting this policy, you are deemed to have read, understood, accepted, and agreed to be bound by all its terms.

**4\. Changes**  
We may change the terms of this policy at any time. We will notify you of any changes by placing a notice in a prominent place on the website or by email. If you do not agree with the change you must stop using the services. If you continue to use the services following notification of a change to the terms, the changed terms will apply to you and you will be deemed to have accepted such terms.

**5\. Collection**

5.1 On entering competitions. Once you enter a competition through the use of the Facebook commenting mechanism, you will no longer be anonymous to us as you will provide us with personal information. This personal information will include:

  * your name, surname,
  * your email address,
  * your IP address.

5.2 Optional details. You may also provide additional information on a voluntary basis such as your name, telephone number and postal address (“optional information”). This includes content or products that you decide to upload or download from our website or when you enter competitions, take advantage of promotions, register and subscribe for certain additional services, or otherwise use the optional features and functionality of the website.

5.3 Cookies. When you access our website we may send one or more cookies (small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters) to your computer to collect certain usage information. We use persistent cookies (which remain after you close your browser and which can be removed manually) and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to our website. We use information gathered by cookies to improve the website. Please note that some of our business partners (e.g. advertisers) use their own cookies or widgets on our website. We have no access to or control over them. Information collected by any such cookie or widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it, and not by us.

5.4 Purpose for collection. We may use any service information and optional information provided by you for such purposes as indicated to you at the time you agree to provide such service information or optional information. We may use your usage information for the purposes described above and to:

  * remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the website;
  * monitor website usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and
  * track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities in connection with your usage of the website.

**6\. Consent to collection**

We will obtain your consent to collect personal information:

  * in accordance with applicable law; and
  * at the time you provide us with any registration information or optional information.

**7\. Use**

7.1 Messages and updates. We may send administrative messages and email updates to you regarding the website.  In some cases, we may also send you primarily promotional messages.  You can choose to opt-out of promotional messages.

**8\. Disclosure**

8.1 Sharing. We do not share your personal information.

8.2 Regulators. If you contact us regarding your experience with using any of our products, we may disclose your personal information as required by law or governmental audit.

8.3 Law enforcement. We may disclose personal information if required:

  * by a subpoena or court order;
  * to comply with any law;
  * to protect the safety of any individual or the general public; and
  * to prevent violation of our service terms.

8.4 No selling. We will not sell personal information.  No personal information will be disclosed to anyone except as provided in this privacy policy.

8.5 Marketing purposes. We may disclose aggregate statistics (information about the customer population in general terms) about the personal information to advertisers or business partners.

8.6 Employees. We may need to disclose personal information to our employees that require the personal information to do their jobs.

8.7 Change of ownership. If we undergo a change in ownership, or a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to, another entity, we may assign our rights to the personal information we process to a successor, purchaser, or separate entity. We will disclose the transfer on the website. If you are concerned about your personal information migrating to a new owner, you may request us to delete your personal information.

**9\. Security of personal information**

We protect your information in the manner specified in our security policy. Generally we use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption to protect personal information and we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files. We authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfil their job responsibilities.

**10\. Retention of personal information**

We will only retain your personal information for as long as it is necessary to fulfil the purposes explicitly set out in this policy, unless:

  * retention of the record is required or authorised by law; or
  * you have consented to the retention of the record.

During the period of retention, we will continue to abide by our non disclosure obligations and will not share or sell your personal information.

**11\. Transfer of personal information outside South Africa**

We will not transfer any personal information across a country border without your prior written consent.

**12\. Limitation**

We are not responsible for, give no warranties, nor make any representations in respect of the privacy policies or practices of linked or any third party websites.

**13\. Enquiries**

If you have any questions or concerns arising from this privacy policy or the way in which we handle personal information, please contact us.
